<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <!-- Replaced New Harvest logs -->
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_CedarWood.label>cedar wood</DankPyon_Log_VV_CedarWood.label>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_CedarWood.description>Fragrant, lightweight, unprocessed wood from the cedar tree. Naturally resistant to decay and insects, it is favored for storage chests, roofing, and construction requiring durability without excess weight.</DankPyon_Log_VV_CedarWood.description>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_CedarWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>cedar</DankPyon_Log_VV_CedarWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_EbonyWood.label>ebony wood</DankPyon_Log_VV_EbonyWood.label>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_EbonyWood.description>Dense and dark unprocessed wood from the ebony tree. Extremely durable and sought after for high-end furniture, construction and tools. Though heavier and harder to work with, its beauty and strength are unmatched.</DankPyon_Log_VV_EbonyWood.description>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_EbonyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>ebony</DankPyon_Log_VV_EbonyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_MahoganyWood.label>mahogany wood</DankPyon_Log_VV_MahoganyWood.label>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_MahoganyWood.description>Richly colored and smooth unprocessed wood from the mahogany tree. Though lighter than ebony, it is highly valued for its balance between beauty, strength, and workability, making it ideal for furniture and decorative construction.</DankPyon_Log_VV_MahoganyWood.description>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_MahoganyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>mahogany</DankPyon_Log_VV_MahoganyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_RosewoodWood.label>rosewood wood</DankPyon_Log_VV_RosewoodWood.label>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_RosewoodWood.description>Elegant and richly colored unprocessed wood from the rosewood tree. Renowned for its deep red to purple hue, it is highly sought after for crafting high-end furniture and decorative items.</DankPyon_Log_VV_RosewoodWood.description>
    <DankPyon_Log_VV_RosewoodWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>rosewood</DankPyon_Log_VV_RosewoodWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <!-- Planks -->
    <VV_CedarWood.label>cedar wood planks</VV_CedarWood.label>
    <VV_CedarWood.description>Fragrant, lightweight processed wood from the cedar tree. Naturally resistant to decay and insects, it is favored for storage chests, roofing, and construction requiring durability without excess weight.</VV_CedarWood.description>
    <VV_CedarWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>cedar</VV_CedarWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_EbonyWood.label>ebony wood planks</VV_EbonyWood.label>
    <VV_EbonyWood.description>Dense and dark processed wood from the ebony tree. Extremely durable and sought after for high-end furniture, construction and tools. Though heavier and harder to work with, its beauty and strength are unmatched.</VV_EbonyWood.description>
    <VV_EbonyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>ebony</VV_EbonyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_MahoganyWood.label>mahogany wood planks</VV_MahoganyWood.label>
    <VV_MahoganyWood.description>Richly colored and smooth processed wood from the mahogany tree. Though lighter than ebony, it is highly valued for its balance between beauty, strength, and workability, making it ideal for furniture and decorative construction.</VV_MahoganyWood.description>
    <VV_MahoganyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>mahogany</VV_MahoganyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_RosewoodWood.label>rosewood wood planks</VV_RosewoodWood.label>
    <VV_RosewoodWood.description>Elegant and richly colored processed wood from the rosewood tree. Renowned for its deep red to purple hue, it is highly sought after for crafting high-end furniture and decorative items.</VV_RosewoodWood.description>
    <VV_RosewoodWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>rosewood</VV_RosewoodWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <DankPyon_SpinningWheel.description>A rolling contraption that processes textiles into fabrics.</DankPyon_SpinningWheel.description>
</LanguageData>