<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <VV_DragonFruitPlant.description>A tropical plant that produces large, vibrant fruits with a sweet and tangy flavor. Dragon fruit plants thrive in hot, sunny climates with well-drained soil.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Dragonfruit plants grow 30% faster in equatorial regions. The size of the equatorial region depends on the planet's overall temperature: below 15ยบ for Normal, below 35ยบ for Warm, below 65ยบ for Hot and all the planet for Very Hot. Planets with below Normal temperature are considered to have no equator.</VV_DragonFruitPlant.description>
    <VV_AmaranthPlant.description>A vibrant, leafy plant that produces small, edible seeds. Amaranth is highly nutritious and can grow in a variety of climates, making it a versatile crop.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Amaranth plants have adapted to drought conditions so well that they recieve a 70% growth penalty when grown within 10 tiles of water.</VV_AmaranthPlant.description>
    <VV_MilletPlant.description>A hardy, drought-resistant plant that grows in a variety of conditions. Its small, sturdy seeds are a great source of nutrition and can thrive in poor soil.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Millet plants have adapted to drought conditions so well that they recieve a 70% growth penalty when grown within 10 tiles of water.</VV_MilletPlant.description>
    <VV_ArtichokePlant.description>A large, perennial plant with spiky leaves that produces edible flower buds. Artichokes thrive in mild climates with plenty of sunlight.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Artichoke plants are very resistant to damage. They take less damage from prolonged lack of light, and will regenerate damage caused by any other means.</VV_ArtichokePlant.description>
    <VV_AsparagusPlant.description>Asparagus is a tender vegetable plant grown for its edible green shoots. It thrives in fertile soil and provides a nutritious harvest once mature.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Artichoke plants are very resistant to damage. They take less damage from prolonged lack of light, and will regenerate damage caused by any other means.</VV_AsparagusPlant.description>
</LanguageData>