<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <!-- Lumber -->
    <VV_CedarLumber.label>cedar lumber</VV_CedarLumber.label>
    <VV_CedarLumber.description>Processed cedar lumber. Fragrant, lightweight and naturally resistant to decay and insects, it is favored for storage chests, roofing, and construction requiring durability without excess weight.</VV_CedarLumber.description>
    <VV_CedarLumber.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>cedar</VV_CedarLumber.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_EbonyLumber.label>ebony lumber</VV_EbonyLumber.label>
    <VV_EbonyLumber.description>Processed ebony lumber. Dense, dark and extremely durable and sought after for high-end furniture, construction and tools. Though heavier and harder to work with, its beauty and strength are unmatched.</VV_EbonyLumber.description>
    <VV_EbonyLumber.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>ebony</VV_EbonyLumber.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_MahoganyLumber.label>mahogany lumber</VV_MahoganyLumber.label>
    <VV_MahoganyLumber.description>Processed mahogany lumber. Though lighter than ebony, it is richly colored and smooth, and highly valued for its balance between beauty, strength, and workability, making it ideal for furniture and decorative construction.</VV_MahoganyLumber.description>
    <VV_MahoganyLumber.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>mahogany</VV_MahoganyLumber.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_RosewoodLumber.label>rosewood lumber</VV_RosewoodLumber.label>
    <VV_RosewoodLumber.description>Processed rosewood lumber. Elegant and richly colored and renowned for its deep red to purple hue, it is highly sought after for crafting high-end furniture and decorative items.</VV_RosewoodLumber.description>
    <VV_RosewoodLumber.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>rosewood</VV_RosewoodLumber.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <!-- Replaced New Harvest logs -->
    <VV_CedarWood.label>cedar logs</VV_CedarWood.label>
    <VV_CedarWood.description>Raw wood from a cedar tree. When processed it becomes useful for building structures, weapons, and even simple prosthetics. Cedar is a durable softwood.</VV_CedarWood.description>
    <VV_CedarWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>cedar</VV_CedarWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_EbonyWood.label>ebony logs</VV_EbonyWood.label>
    <VV_EbonyWood.description>Raw wood from a ebony tree. When processed it becomes useful for building structures, weapons, and even simple prosthetics. Ebony is among the most durable hardwoods.</VV_EbonyWood.description>
    <VV_EbonyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>ebony</VV_EbonyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_MahoganyWood.label>mahogany logs</VV_MahoganyWood.label>
    <VV_MahoganyWood.description>Raw wood from a mahogany tree. When processed it becomes useful for building structures, weapons, and even simple prosthetics. Mahogany is a very durable hardwood.</VV_MahoganyWood.description>
    <VV_MahoganyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>mahogany</VV_MahoganyWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
    <VV_RosewoodWood.label>rosewood logs</VV_RosewoodWood.label>
    <VV_RosewoodWood.description>Raw wood from a rosewood tree. When processed it becomes useful for building structures, weapons, and even simple prosthetics. Rosewood is a durable hardwood.</VV_RosewoodWood.description>
    <VV_RosewoodWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>rosewood</VV_RosewoodWood.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>
</LanguageData>