<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <VV_BroccoliPlant.description>A food crop that produces compact green florets. Its longer growing time makes it better suited for stable, planned farming.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Broccoli plants will continue to grow at 10% speed through winter. They need to be planted during growing season, though.</VV_BroccoliPlant.description>
    <VV_LeekPlant.description>A hardy vegetable with long white stalks and green tops. Leeks mature quickly and provide a steady, modest harvest, making them a reliable addition to any farm.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Leeks will continue to grow at 10% speed through winter. They need to be planted during growing season, though.</VV_LeekPlant.description>
    <VV_ParsnipPlant.description>A slow-growing root vegetable with creamy edible roots. Parsnips take time to mature but offer steady harvests for the colony.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Parsnips will continue to grow at 10% speed through winter. They need to be planted during growing season, though.</VV_ParsnipPlant.description>
    <VV_RedCabbagePlant.description>A hardy vegetable producing compact, purple heads. Red cabbage grows steadily and yields a reliable harvest, making it a solid choice for any farm.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Red cabbages will continue to grow at 10% speed through winter. They need to be planted during growing season, though.</VV_RedCabbagePlant.description>
    <VV_SpinachPlant.description>A quick-growing leafy vegetable. Spinach matures quickly and provides a reliable, modest harvest, making it an easy addition to any farm.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; Spinach will continue to grow at 10% speed through winter. It needs to be planted during growing season, though.</VV_SpinachPlant.description>
    <VV_WhiteTurnipPlant.description>A slow-growing root vegetable with white edible roots. White turnips require patience but offer dependable harvests for the colony.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; White turnips will continue to grow at 10% speed through winter. They need to be planted during growing season, though.</VV_WhiteTurnipPlant.description>
</LanguageData>